// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is",
    answer: "font-size",
    options: [
      "text-style",
      "text-size",
      "font-size",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What does CSS stand for?",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
    options: [
      "Common Style Sheet",
      "Colorful Style Sheet",
      "Computer Style Sheet",
      "Cascading Style Sheet"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Is HTML a scripting language",
    answer: "No",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "Maybe",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The latest HTML standard is",
    answer: "HTML 5",
    options: [
      "XML",
      "HTML 5",
      "SGML",
      "HTML 3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "HTML was developed by",
    answer: "Tim Berners-Lee",
    options: [
      "Tim Bruce",
      "Tim Berners-Lee",
      "Hakon Wium Lie",
      "Guido van Rossum"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which tool can you use to ensure code quality?",
    answer: "ESLint",
    options: [
      "Angular",
      "jQuery",
      "RequireJS",
      "ESLint"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "HTML uses",
    answer: "Pre-specified Tags",
    options: [
      "User Defined Tags",
      "Pre-specified Tags",
      "Tags Only For Linking",
      "Fixed Tags Defined By The Language"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The CSS property used to specify whether a text is written in horizontal or vertical direction",
    answer: "writing-mode",
    options: [
      "writing-mode",
      "text-indent",
      "word-break",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The HTML Geolocation API is used to get the",
    answer: "geographical position",
    options: [
      "drag and drop position",
      "geographical position",
      "create graphics",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following CSS property is used to add shadows to the text?",
    answer: "text-shadow",
    options: [
      "text-stroke",
      "text-overflow",
      "text-shadow",
      "text-decoration"
    ]
  },
];